<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>图林根の烤肠</title>
        <link>https://thueringerbratwurst.com/</link>
        <description>This is my cool site</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>crosser_wack.0m@icloud.com (图林根の烤肠)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>crosser_wack.0m@icloud.com (图林根の烤肠)</webMaster><copyright>2023ⒸAll Rights Reserved</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 23:08:07 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="https://thueringerbratwurst.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>iOS - Einbürgerung in Deutschland</title>
    <link>https://thueringerbratwurst.com/eide/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 23:08:07 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>图林根の烤肠</author>
    <guid>https://thueringerbratwurst.com/eide/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Einbürgerung in Deutschland The perfect study companion for successful integration into German society and obtaining German citizenship.
Descrpition The Einbürgerung in Deutschland is the perfect study companion for successful integration into German society and obtaining German citizenship. Whether you are a new immigrant or someone looking to improve your knowledge of the German language and culture, this app will meet your needs. It offers a large number of practice exam questions covering all aspects of the naturalization exam, including cultural, historical, political and social knowledge.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>202309 Hamburg</title>
    <link>https://thueringerbratwurst.com/202309-hamburg/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 18:30:00 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>图林根の烤肠</author>
    <guid>https://thueringerbratwurst.com/202309-hamburg/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>202308 Bonn</title>
    <link>https://thueringerbratwurst.com/202308-bonn/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 18:30:00 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>图林根の烤肠</author>
    <guid>https://thueringerbratwurst.com/202308-bonn/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>202307 Köln</title>
    <link>https://thueringerbratwurst.com/202307-koeln/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 18:30:00 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>图林根の烤肠</author>
    <guid>https://thueringerbratwurst.com/202307-koeln/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>2021-2022</title>
    <link>https://thueringerbratwurst.com/2021-2022/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 18:30:00 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>图林根の烤肠</author>
    <guid>https://thueringerbratwurst.com/2021-2022/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Shortcut - MH Watermark</title>
    <link>https://thueringerbratwurst.com/watermark/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 19:47:31 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>图林根の烤肠</author>
    <guid>https://thueringerbratwurst.com/watermark/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Watermarked images with added image information MH Watermark This shortcut code that can be used directly without downloading any app and support iPhone, iPad and Mac. Features Support to add the logo watermark of major camera manufacturers: Hasselblad, Leica, Sony, Nikon, Canon, Fujifilm, Panasonic etc. Displays shooting equipment and lens models based on picture information via EXIF. Fully customizable display of corresponding shooting parameters Automatically or manually add geographic locations]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>MacOS - Piano LED for Arduino (Piano Visualizer)</title>
    <link>https://thueringerbratwurst.com/pla/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 21:06:07 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>图林根の烤肠</author>
    <guid>https://thueringerbratwurst.com/pla/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Descrpition Piano LED for Arduino (PLA) is a piano visualizer, it is free, lightweight, without Ad. application that allows you to controll LED-Strips during you playing digital piano (you still need an Arduino board, like UNO). It is able to receive MIDI message from your digital piano and transmit the MIDI data to Arduino, so that Arduino is able to control LEDs with the MIDI-Streaming.
Download Links Piano LED for Arduino v1.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Secret Hider</title>
    <link>https://thueringerbratwurst.com/secret_hider/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 03:17:40 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>图林根の烤肠</author>
    <guid>https://thueringerbratwurst.com/secret_hider/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Download App Store Product features: Three different passwords adapt to various situations: Normal password: Login with this password will show your normal files. Super Password: It will show/hide your secret files. Emergency password: This password will delete all your secret files before you log in to the application to completely avoid data leakage. Non-subscription system, once purchased, lifetime use. 3. Completely offline, eliminate your personal privacy leakage. 4. Double encryption]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>VIN Checker</title>
    <link>https://thueringerbratwurst.com/vin/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 18:39:19 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>图林根の烤肠</author>
    <guid>https://thueringerbratwurst.com/vin/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[If you want to leave a message, please use English, German or Chinese
Download App Store
Description If you intend to export cars to China, this application is your best helper. This application can quickly verify the vehicle identification code and tells you whether your car can be exported to China. It may save you a lot of time to contact with Chinese customers.
Features: Fast and convenient, fully localized operation.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
