<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - 图林根の烤肠</title>
        <link>http://www.thueringerbratwurst.com/en/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | 图林根の烤肠</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>crosser_wack.0m@icloud.com (图林根の烤肠)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>crosser_wack.0m@icloud.com (图林根の烤肠)</webMaster><copyright>2023ⒸAll Rights Reserved</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 21:06:07 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.thueringerbratwurst.com/en/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>MacOS - Piano LED for Arduino (Piano Visualizer)</title>
    <link>http://www.thueringerbratwurst.com/en/pla/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 21:06:07 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>图林根の烤肠</author>
    <guid>http://www.thueringerbratwurst.com/en/pla/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Descrpition Piano LED for Arduino (PLA) is a piano visualizer, it is free, lightweight, without Ad. application that allows you to controll LED-Strips during you playing digital piano (you still need an Arduino board, like UNO). It is able to receive MIDI message from your digital piano and transmit the MIDI data to Arduino, so that Arduino is able to control LEDs with the MIDI-Streaming.
Download Links Piano LED for Arduino v1.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Secret Hider</title>
    <link>http://www.thueringerbratwurst.com/en/secret_hider/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 03:17:40 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>图林根の烤肠</author>
    <guid>http://www.thueringerbratwurst.com/en/secret_hider/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Download App Store
Product features: Three different passwords adapt to various situations:
Normal password: Login with this password will show your normal files. Super Password: It will show/hide your secret files. Emergency password: This password will delete all your secret files before you log in to the application to completely avoid data leakage. Non-subscription system, once purchased, lifetime use. 3.
Completely offline, eliminate your personal privacy leakage. 4.
Double encryption to protect your privacy to the maximum.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>VIN Checker</title>
    <link>http://www.thueringerbratwurst.com/en/vin/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 18:39:19 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>图林根の烤肠</author>
    <guid>http://www.thueringerbratwurst.com/en/vin/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[If you want to leave a message, please use English, German or Chinese
Download App Store
Description If you intend to export cars to China, this application is your best helper. This application can quickly verify the vehicle identification code and tells you whether your car can be exported to China. It may save you a lot of time to contact with Chinese customers.
Features: Fast and convenient, fully localized operation.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>This domain is for sale...</title>
    <link>http://www.thueringerbratwurst.com/en/sale/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2013 13:33:34 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>图林根の烤肠</author>
    <guid>http://www.thueringerbratwurst.com/en/sale/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Please send me email and tell me:
which domain you want to buy? price with US Dollar $ ]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
